const Mathematics = [
    {
      question: "Math Who was the first man to enter a moon ?",
      options: ["Charles Darwin", "Robert Mongo", "David Schawam", "Uriel Sam"],
      correct: "Charles Darwin",
      questionId: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Math In whihc year did the Corona Virus Start ?",
      options: ["1999", "2003", "2020", "2019"],
      correct: "2019",
      questionId: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Which Country has the greatest Population ?",
      options: ["China", "Russia", "Nigeria", "Isreal"],
      correct: "China",
      questionId: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Math When is the next U.S.A Presidential Debate",
      options: ["October 2", "October 6", "October 4", "October 1"],
      correct: "October 1",
      questionId: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who is the President of Nigeria ?",
      options: ["Buhari", "Bwari", "Boohari", "Bhuari"],
      correct: "Buhari",
      questionId: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who is the Presdient of the U.S.A",
      options: ["Doanld Trump", "Donny Biden", "Tar Coo", "Biden Rei"],
      correct: "Donald Trump",
      questionId: 6,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who did Trump Compete with in the Recent Presdiential Debate ?",
      options: ["Joe Bidden", "Rebecca Rice", "tee Harley", "Pop Dee"],
      correct: "Joe Bidden",
      questionId: 7,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who was the first man to enter a moon ?",
      options: ["Charles Darwin", "Robert Mongo", "David Schawam", "Uriel Sam"],
      correct: "Charles Darwin",
      questionId: 8,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who was the first man to enter a moon ?",
      options: ["Charles Darwin", "Robert Mongo", "David Schawam", "Uriel Sam"],
      correct: "Charles Darwin",
      questionId: 9,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who was the first man to enter a moon ?",
      options: ["Charles Darwin", "Robert Mongo", "David Schawam", "Uriel Sam"],
      correct: "Charles Darwin",
      questionId: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Who was the first man to enter a moon ?",
      options: ["Charles Darwin", "Robert Mongo", "David Schawam", "Uriel Sam"],
      correct: "Charles Darwin",
      questionId: 11,
    },
  ]
  
//   var Bquest = Biology[Math.floor(Math.random()*Biology.length)]
//   var Bquest = (n = 5) =>{
//     (Biology.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
//    }

  module.exports = Mathematics
 
  